Anton OrlovFull-Stack Developer

3476532650

aorlov927@gmail.com github.com/antonaorlov linkedin.com/in/Anton-Orlov | Citizen Smosswattsweddings.site.com Brooklyn, New York

Profile

As a Graphic/UI-UX Designer turned Full-Stack Developer, I am driven by a passion for turning ideas into reality. While I am continuously learning and improving my coding skills, I am most fulfilled when creating responsive and user-friendly websites.

I am driven by a desire to constantly push beyond my perceived limits and take on challenges that test my capabilities. I find great satisfaction in tackling difficult projects and striving towards ambitious goals that push me to reach my full potential.

My areas of specialization include Javascript (React), Node.js, PostgreSQL, SQL, HTML, CSS, Python and the use of various packages for website deployment on both the front-end and back-end.

Experience

September 2022 - December 2022 PTP357 Studio Internship Graphic Designer/ Web Designer

- * Worked on projects in advertising wedding shows, event planning, Photography.
- * Website development using JavaScript, HTML, CSS. Graphics designed using Adobe software

June 2022 - September 2022 | Graphic Designer/Web Designer Verasoni Internship

- * Worked on 20+ projects from marketing, social media, Web Design, Logo Design, Business Cards and more,
- * Using software such as Adobe, languages such as HTML, CSS.

July 2019 - August 2019 | Web Developer Verizon, Accenture Future Ready Lab Internship

- * Participated in Verizon's student program called
- "Verizon Future Ready Labs"
- * Won the competition of creating a Smart Can concept to make NYC a smarter city
- * Developed a website using HTML, CSS, java script, Node.js and deployed to cleanercan.webflow.io
- * Received a National Academy Financial (NAF) Certification

Education

2020-2024 | Bachelor of Science in Computer Science, CUNY Hunter Colllege 2016-2020 | James Madison High School

Skills:

Javascript(React), Node.js, PostgreSQL, SQL, CSS, HTML, GIT, various npm packages, Adobe Softwares

Certifications:

Microsoft Office Excel, Word and PowerPoint